<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>causal diagrams on Bolor-Erdene Zolbayar</title>
    <link>https://bolor23erdene.github.io/tags/causal-diagrams/</link>
    <description>Recent content in causal diagrams on Bolor-Erdene Zolbayar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bolor23erdene.github.io/tags/causal-diagrams/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is GANs?</title>
      <link>https://bolor23erdene.github.io/posts/gans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bolor23erdene.github.io/posts/gans/</guid>
      <description>The goal of one of my research is to generate adversarial network traffic that fools the network detection system. I used deep generative model GANs to create the adversarial samples. GANs are known to be best for learning finite amount of training data, interpolating the training data&amp;rsquo;s distribution, and creating samples that are indistinguishable from the original training data. Basically, with GANs, I was able to generate huge amount adversarial traffic by keeping the features that are intrinsic to the attacks and changing the unimportant features so that the traffic bypasses the detection system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Book of Why</title>
      <link>https://bolor23erdene.github.io/posts/book-of-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bolor23erdene.github.io/posts/book-of-why/</guid>
      <description>https://oeis.org/wiki/List_of_LaTeX_mathematical_symbols https://lmyint.github.io/post/book-of-why/
I just finished reading The Book of Why by Judea Pearl and Dana Mackenzie, and I really enjoyed it. I had been wanting to read it for some time now because I know very little about methodology relating to causal diagrams and structure learning. The book provides an overview of the main ideas that formed and historical events that led up to what Pearl calls the &amp;ldquo;Causal Revolution&amp;rdquo;, a burgeoning of the direct interrogation of causation as opposed to its implicit renouncement in science for a period before then.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>